Love You Like a Love Song
压制:随Feng
Selena Gomez
It's been said and done
似乎人们们都已清楚
Every beautiful thought's been already sung
所有美妙的情感都已经被演绎成歌曲
And I guess right now here's another one
然而 我想另外一首歌曲此刻才被唱出
So your melody will play on and on
你的旋律才不会停止
with best we own
用我们最美的声音
You are beautiful
你的美丽
like a dream come alive  incredible
宛若美梦成真 如梦如幻
A center full of miracle  lyrical
幻如奇迹诞生 诗情画意
You've saved my life again
又一次 你拯救我于水火之间
And I want you to know baby
而我要让你知道
I  I love you like a love song, baby
我像热恋情歌一样热恋着你
And I keep it in re-pe-pe-peat
总是禁不住重复聆听 聆听 聆听
I  I love you like a love song  baby
我像热恋情歌一样热恋着你
And I keep it in re-pe-pe-peat
总是禁不住重复聆听 聆听 聆听
Cursing me  boy you played
我无法自拔 宛如交响曲
through my mind like a symphony
一样涤荡着我的心灵
There's no way to describe what you do to me
你对我的爱总让我无法形容
You just do to me  what you do
一直伴随着我
And it feels like I've been rescued
感觉我已获得新生
I've been set free
我破茧而出
I am hyptonized by your destiny
你是我的真命天子 我被深深地迷住
You are magical, lyrical  beautiful
你就是那么不可思议 诗情画意 帅气动人
You are  I want you to know baby
你就是...而我想让你知道
I  I love you like a love song  baby
我像热恋情歌一样热恋着你
I I love you like a love song  baby
I  I love you like a love song baby
我像热恋情歌一样热恋着你
And I keep it in re-pe-pe-peat
总是禁不住重复聆听 聆听 聆听
I  I love you like a love song  baby
我像热恋情歌一样热恋着你
And I keep it in re-pe-pe-peat
总是禁不住重复聆听 聆听 聆听
No one can pause
无人可以阻挡
You stand alone  to every record I own
别的韵律都黯然失色
Music to my hear that's what you are
你就是那震撼我心灵的乐章
A song that goes on and on
一首永恒不停的乐曲
I  I love you like a love song  baby
我像热恋情歌一样热恋着你
And I keep it in re-pe-pe-peat
总是禁不住重复聆听 聆听 聆听
I  I love you like a love song  baby
我像热恋情歌一样热恋着你
I love you  like a love song
压制:随Feng